[{"Response":"Very safe","Percentage of respondents":47.9,"Question":"To what extent would you say you are, or would be, safe from crime when walking in your local area   ? - During the day -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Fairly safe","Percentage of respondents":44.2,"Question":"To what extent would you say you are, or would be, safe from crime when walking in your local area   ? - During the day -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Not particularly safe","Percentage of respondents":5.9,"Question":"To what extent would you say you are, or would be, safe from crime when walking in your local area   ? - During the day -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Not safe at all","Percentage of respondents":1.3,"Question":"To what extent would you say you are, or would be, safe from crime when walking in your local area   ? - During the day -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Very safe","Percentage of respondents":14.7,"Question":"To what extent would you say you are, or would be, safe from crime when walking in your local area   ? - In the evening -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Fairly safe","Percentage of respondents":48.5,"Question":"To what extent would you say you are, or would be, safe from crime when walking in your local area   ? - In the evening -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Not particularly safe","Percentage of respondents":24.3,"Question":"To what extent would you say you are, or would be, safe from crime when walking in your local area   ? - In the evening -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Not safe at all","Percentage of respondents":10.5,"Question":"To what extent would you say you are, or would be, safe from crime when walking in your local area   ? - In the evening -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Strongly agree","Percentage of respondents":8.5,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that you have confidence in the police in your local area?","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Tend to agree","Percentage of respondents":25.6,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that you have confidence in the police in your local area?","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Neither agree nor disagree","Percentage of respondents":28.3,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that you have confidence in the police in your local area?","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Tend to disagree","Percentage of respondents":17.5,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that you have confidence in the police in your local area?","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Strongly disagree","Percentage of respondents":15.6,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that you have confidence in the police in your local area?","Time period":2022}]